goodluckielts.com 2018-01-28

# Good Luck IELTS - Advice, Tips, and Guides to the IELTS Exam

#### Privacy Policy

> If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at langvid AT langvid DOT com.
> 
> At www.GoodLuckIELTS.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.GoodLuckIELTS.com and how it is used.
> 
> Log Files   
>  Like many other Web sites, www.GoodLuckIELTS.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users� movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
> 
> **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
>  www.GoodLuckIELTS.com uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
> 
> We also use third party advertisements. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and whether you have Flash installed. This information is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York ESL school ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing teaching ads to someone who frequents teaching sites).
> 
> DoubleClick DART cookies  
>  We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about IELTS, you may see IELTS advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about IELTS). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
> 
> You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
> 
> Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. www.GoodLuckIELTS.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.GoodLuckIELTS.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
